let's look at the solution to our smt
and casual ation ship quiz we have three
programs program a has a working set
that doesn't fit in the cache that means
that program a will have a lot of cache
misses no matter what we do program be
alone would fit in the cache program see
alone would fit in the cache programs B
and C would fit in the cache but if we
run all three together then the total
working set size is 15 kilobytes which
doesn't fit in the cache so all of them
get poor cache behavior so really we
should not be running all three together
we should not be running a and B
together because then C gets to run
alone so we don't benefit from sm t and
b runs with a sobe also has a lot of
cache misses we should run a and then b
and c that way a which has to get poor
cache behavior gets poor cache behavior
alone but B and C benefit from smt and
fit in the cache so they still get good
cache behavior so we should do this just
like we shouldn't run be with a we
shouldn't run serie de and then running
a and then B and then c is not
benefiting from smt although B and C
would fit in the cache so that's why
this is the only correct answer